Guide to the A. Poulin Papers and BOA Editions Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 1993 Acquisition, 1960-1991; 2; 52.46; (49 boxes)
  - Yannis Ritsos: Selected Poems, 1938-1988, Kimon Friar and Kostas Myrsiades, eds., proofs, 14 (Box 82)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: "Hurricane Walk," typescript (Box 82)
  - John Logan: The Collected Poems, printed version, 2 (Box 82)
  - Books (Box 83)
  - Poulin lecture on Lowell & Logan, Alfred University, 10/8/85,"(audiocassette), 1985 October 8; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002091243361)
    Use of originals restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
  - Fuhrer Bunker Choruses [reel-to-reel audiotape], 1981 March 31; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002091243353)
  - Daphne (audiocassette), undated; 1 (Box 84, Item barcode 39002091243379)
  - Anghelaki-Rooke, Katerina: Beings and Things On Their Own, typescript and proofs, 4 (Box 85)
  - Laux, Dorianne: Awake, boards (Box 85)
  - Lee, Li-Young: Rose, proofs (Box 85)
  - Logan, John: John Logan: The Collected Fiction, proofs (Box 86)
  - Piccione, Anthony: Seeing It Was So, proofs (Box 86)
  - Tremblay, William: Duhamel, typescript and proofs, 2 (Box 86)
  - Printed material (Box 87)
  - Assorted cover proofs (Box 87)
  - Assorted cover designs and proofs, 10 (Box 88 (Oversize))
- May 1997 Acquisition, 1951-1996; 3; 39.38; (44 boxes)
  Boxes 111 and 126 (audio and video cassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 132 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Manuscripts and other papers relating to Al Poulin and BOA Editions, including proofs, ephemera, photographs, audiovisual material, and computer disks.
  Former call number Uncat ZA MS 528.
  - Stroud, Joseph: Below Cold Mountain, bound manuscript copy, 1995 September (Box 89)
  - Beckman, Joshua Saul: Long Live Exact Demonstration, manuscript copy, 1996 February (Box 89)
  - Parker, Alan Michael: Days Like Prose, manuscript copy, 1996 January (Box 89)
  - Smith, Yohannes Sharriff: Brand X, bound manuscript copy, 1996 April (Box 89)
  - Razier, Lucy F.: Poems for the Angels, manuscript copy, 1996 April (Box 89)
  - Axelrod, Mark R., translation: A Voyage Around My Room by Xavier de Maistre, bound manuscript copy, 1996 April (Box 89)
  - Dean, Joseph W.: Mother's Poetry, Early Settlers and Their Life on the West Texas Plains, manuscript copy, 1996 April (Box 89)
  - Wee, Rebecca Liv: Intarsia, manuscript copy, 1996 March (Box 89)
  - Brown, Stephen R.: On Rowing Boats At Night, manuscript copy, 1996 April (Box 89)
  - Keller, Tsipi, translation: Monologues and Other Poems by T. Carmi, manuscript copy, 1996 May (Box 89)
  - Carson, Meredith: Infinite Morning, bound manuscript copy, 1996 February (Box 89)
  - Frederiksen, Nancy: Dawn, manuscript copy, 1996 April (Box 89)
  - Eimers, Nancy: No Moon, manuscript copy, 1996 January (Box 89)
  - Nurkse, D. The Rules of Paradise, bound manuscript copy The Swiftness With Which Those Cities Fell, bound manuscript copy, [1996]; 2 (Box 89)
  - Maddox, Marjorie: Transplant, Transport, Transubstantiation, manuscript copy, 1996 April (Box 89)
  - Authors' submissions: miscellaneous, [1995-1996]; 19 (Box 89)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks, Masters, undated; 3 (Box 90)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks, page proofs with corrections, [1993]; 2 (Box 90)
  - BOA Writers w/ index #1, undated (Box 90)
  - BOA Writers #2, undated (Box 90)
  - Sutter: Book of Names, copy of galley proofs with corrections, 1993 (Box 90)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks, masters for uncorrected proofs, [1993] (Box 90)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks, corrected galley proofs, [1993] (Box 90)
  - Wordworks, interns' original dummy, extra pages, worksheets, undated (Box 90)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks, corrections, undated (Box 90)
  - Audio CD: The Sonorous Landscape, chamber music, undated (Box 91)
  - Voices Over Water: Poetry By D. Nurkse, 1993 (Box 91)
  - BOA Editions, Ltd.: A Small Press, A World of Poetry: Checklist 1977-1990: booklet [10 copies], [circa 1990] (Box 91)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely. Not A Stranger, 2nd version, manuscript copy, undated (Box 91)
  - Sutter: Book of Names, copy of typescript with copy editing, 1993 (Box 91)
  - Sutter: Book of Names, typescript with original copy editing, 1993 (Box 91)
  - Sutter: Book of Names, Galley Proofs with Corrections, 1993 (Box 91)
  - Sutter: Book of Names, galley masters, undated (Box 91)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: Not A Stranger, version #1, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 91)
  - Piccione, Anthony: For The Kingdom, Dec. 1992, good 1st copy, undated (Box 91)
  - Miscellaneous mailings and submissions to Al Poulin and BOA, [1993-1994]; 10 (Box 91)
  - Jauss, David: Improvising Rivers, undated (Box 91)
  - Liu, Timothy. With Chaos in Each Kiss, manuscript copy, undated (Box 91)
  - Staff Reports, [1993-1994] (Box 91)
  - Contents: Addonizio, BOA poets, Non-BOA poets, undated (Box 91)
  - NYE, undated (Box 92)
  - Anghelaki-Rooke, Katerina: In This House, and Settling Time's Account, translation [2 manuscript copies], [1992-1993] (Box 92)
  - Lyon, Rick: File relating to Bell 8, submission, manuscript copy, [1994] (Box 92)
  - Addonizio, Kim: "What Do Women Want?", broadside, hand painted, 1994 (Box 92)
  - Laux, Dorianne: manuscript and submissions, [undated?] (Box 92)
  - Kelly, Brigit: publishing material, [1994] (Box 92)
  - Kelly, Brigit: manuscript copies of Song (orig. and corrected 2nd version), 1994 March; 2 (Box 92)
  - Lee, Li-Young: submission and manuscript copy, [1990-1994] (Box 92)
  - "Fagan, Cathy": Moving and St Rage, typescript and correspondence, 1995 March (Box 92)
  - Fritz, Andrew: Peacocks in America, typescript, undated (Box 92)
  - Keener, LuAnn: Homeland, typescript, 1995 February (Box 92)
  - Oness, Chad: Not Grace Exactly, typescript, 1995 February (Box 92)
  - Merrin, Jeredith: two typescripts, correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 92)
  - Hendricks, Brent: The Superbeautiful Clash of Selves, typescript, 1995 February (Box 92)
  - Beggs, Marck L.: The Air Ballooned with Arias, typescript, 1995 January (Box 92)
  - Szporluk, Larissa: Prowler's Universe, typescript, 1995-1996; 2 (Box 92)
  - Cording, Robert: Heavy Grace, typescript, 1995 July (Box 92)
  - Hamill, Paul: The Middle Distance Runner, typescript, 1995 February (Box 92)
  - Business correspondence: submissions, 1993-1995; 20 (Box 93)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Authors' submissions: miscellaneous, 1995; 6 (Box 93)
  - Bedient, Cal: Candy Necklace, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 93)
  - Van Winckel, Nance: After A Spell, manuscript copy, [1994-1995] (Box 93)
  - Hopper, John: The Ympes of Wanton Youthe: Poems 1963-1993: bound manuscript copy, submission for BOA Publication, 1994 (Box 93)
  - Turczyn, Christine: The Bright Colors Of Hunger, submission, dissertation, manuscript copy, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Marcus, Peter: Dark Remedies, bound manuscript copy, 1995 May (Box 93)
  - Soviero, Marcelle M.: The Body That Wants, manuscript copy, 1995 June (Box 93)
  - Crosby, William: files and records, [1991-1994] (Box 93)
  - SPD Complete Catalog and Prentice Hall Annotated Teacher's Edition: sample selections, literature, 1994 (Box 93)
  - Snodgrass, undated (Box 93)
  - Staff Reports, [1992-1993]; 2 (Box 94)
  - Addonizio: page proofs, manuscript copy of The Philosopher's Club: Poems by Kim Addonizio, 1994 (Box 94)
  - BOA Editions Ltd.: 15th anniversary catalog w/ new titles, backlists, and listing of new poets [13 copies], 1992 (Box 94)
  - Lyon, Rick: Bell 8, page proofs, manuscript copy, in env. titled "Lyon Boards", 1994 (Box 94)
  - BOA Stationery Samples, undated (Box 94)
  - Mathieu, Bertrand: miscellaneous files, undated (Box 94)
  - Bly, Robert: miscellaneous files, including manuscript copy of Gratitude to Old Teachers: Poems by Robert Bly, [1993] (Box 94)
  - Marketing materials, [1989-1995]; 6 (Box 94)
    1-2: Marketing Revision Materials and Info.
    Lila Wallace Applications. Paper. 1991-1992
    3: CLMP: The Council of Literary Magazines and Publishers.
    4: Marketing Plan info., financial statements. 1989-1995
    5: CLMP Consultants: 82 pp.
    6: Timeline, 1990-1991
  - Miscellaneous: pamphlet and correspondence, [1993] (Box 94)
  - Lyon, Rick. Bell 8: Poems by Rick Lyon, manuscript copy "Archive: Bell 8: Extra sheets", 1994 (Box 94)
  - BOA Files: news from BOA Editions and miscellaneous reviews [2 sets], 1992-1994; 7 (Box 94)
  - Bly Miscellaneous: typescript copy. Al's computer script of Gratitude to Old Teachers [Poems by Robert Bly], 1993 (Box 95)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence: including "Misc. BOA Rochester" and "Laux Misc.", [1993-1994] (Box 95)
  - Laux, Dorianne: What We Carry, typescript copy and galley proofs, [1994]; 3 (Box 95)
  - Bly miscellaneous and Snodgrass miscellaneous materials, [1993-1994] (Box 95)
  - Lyon typescript copy and Williams foreword original. Also includes miscellaneous corresp., [1993-1994] (Box 95)
  - "What We Carry Cover proofs; Bell 8 Misc.; Hébert/Addonizio Misc.", [1993-1994] (Box 95)
  - Cendrars, Blaise/Mathieu, Bertrand. XMas at the Four Corners of the Earth: uncorrected proofs [w/ front cover], 1994 (Box 95)
  - Bell 8 Galley Proofs, 1994 May (Box 95)
  - Nye, Naomi Shihab: Red Suitcase, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 95)
  - Laux: What We Carry, page proofs, manuscript copy, 1994 (Box 95)
  - Hébert: Day Has No Equal But Night, uncorrected proofs, 1994; 2 (Box 95)
  - Butler, G. Larry: Here Lies Madness, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 95)
  - Account Master Insurance Program: application, BOA insurance policy in envelope marked "Old BOA Insurance Policies", 1994 (Box 95)
  - Irwin, Mark: Quick, Now, Always, photograph; (2) Diskettes for The Quicken Tree (removed from folder), undated (Box 95)
    Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    Available through Access Services:
    1997.ycal.0521-a.0008: Quicken Tree
    1997.ycal.0521-a.0009: Quicken Tree
  - Irwin, Mark: Quick, Now, Always, 3 bound copies, uncorrected proofs, [1995-1996] (Box 95)
  - Fall 1995 BOA catalogue; miscellaneous book covers, undated (Box 95)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, [1993-1995] (Box 95)
  - Irwin, Mark: Quick, Now, Always, sample layout pages, 1 hard copy w/ corrections, 1 set of galleys, [1996]; 2 (Box 95)
  - Irwin, Mark: "Cover Photos for Quick, Now, Always" [2 folders]; 2nd folder reads, "Quick, Now, Always/ Final 10/21/95", 1995-1996 (Box 95)
  - Irwin, Mark: Quick, Now, Always, various versions, edited manuscript copies, including authors' suggestions, [1996]; 5 (Box 95)
  - Sample book covers, authors' notes, undated; 2 (Box 95)
  - 1 pg. email message from Gerhard Lenski to BOA Editions, 1996 January (Box 96)
  - 2 more folders w/ miscellaneous materials, [1996] (Box 96)
  - Crow, Mary: I Have Tasted the Apple, miscellaneous correspondence, galleys, book covers, [1996]; 3 (Box 96)
  - Crow, Mary: I Have Tasted the Apple, various editions, manuscript copies, [1996]; 5 (Box 96)
  - Crow, Mary: I Have Tasted the Apple, galleys. In envelope titled, "5th Febr.", 1996 (Box 96)
  - Inez, Colette: Statement for Mary Crow's Collection of Poems, "I Have Tasted the Apple", 1995 December (Box 96)
  - Crow, Mary: I Have Tasted the Apple, master copy for printer, 1996; 2 (Box 96)
  - Crow, Mary: I Have Tasted the Apple, master copy submitted to Al Poulin, 1996; 2 (Box 96)
  - Heyen, William: Crazy Horse in Stillness, submission, typescript: reading copy, undated (Box 96)
  - Newsletters from BOA Editions, undated (Box 96)
  - Miscellaneous greeting cards, brochures, correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 96)
  - Correspondence: various correspondents and submissions, 1993-1996; 17 (Box 96)
  - Maclean, Robert: Correspondence and various submissions, typescripts and manuscripts, 1996 January; 3 (Box 96)
  - Greene, Jeffrey: American Spirituals, typescript and correspondence, 1996 February (Box 96)
  - Smith, R. Lester: Ducks in a Row, published, bound copy, 1996 February (Box 97)
  - Heyen, William: Crazy Horse in Stillness, miscellaneous business papers, galleys, book covers, 1995 September; 2 (Box 97)
  - Makuck, Peter: Against Distance, typescript and correspondence, 1995 December (Box 97)
  - Bond, Bruce: Radiography, typescript and correspondence, undated (Box 97)
  - Gonzalez, Ray: The Heat of Arrivals, original typescript, undated (Box 97)
  - Clifton, Lucille: The Terrible Stories, corrected page proofs, correspondence, 1995 August-October; 2 (Box 97)
  - Bosselaar, Laure-Anne: The Hour Between Dog and Wolf, typescript, undated (Box 97)
  - Personal Correspondence to Al and Boo Poulin, 1991-1996 January; 5 (Box 97)
  - "Box 4, Poulin Archives": personal correspondence, 1991-1996; 2 (Box 98)
  - "Miscellaneous Correspondence/Poulin Archives/Box 4", 1990-1995; 2 (Box 98)
  - NON-BOA Poets, 1991-1996 (Box 98)
  - Hébert, Anne: Day Has No Equal but Night, galleys, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Published copy of Mid-American Review: poetry anthology, 1995 (Box 98)
  - Miscellaneous: 10 photographed drawings, [1973] (Box 98)
  - Poetry by Al Poulin: poems, correspondence, clippings, copies of originals, newsletter, 1977-1995 (Box 98)
  - St Francis College Alumni Directory; Memorial service program for Sister Lillian Allard, 1977-1994 (Box 98)
  - The Cantos by Ezra Pound; Ezra Pound's Interview, 1988 (Box 98)
  - Poulin, Al, translation: Free Hands, typescript, undated (Box 98)
  - Laughlin, James: biographical information, 1989-1990 (Box 98)
  - Quarterly Review of Literature, undated (Box 98)
  - A. Poulin, Jr.: Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 98)
  - Choice: correspondence, 1977 May-September (Box 98)
  - Poulin, Al, Jr.: A Nest of Sonnets, published copy, 1985 (Box 98)
  - Poulin, Al, Jr.: The Village Idiot- Scenes from an Imaginary Autobiography, corrected typescript, undated (Box 98)
  - Poulin, Al, Jr.: The Platea, typescript, undated (Box 98)
  - Huff, Steven: I'm Only Saying, typescript, undated (Box 98)
  - Rilke, Rainer Maria: The Duino Elegies, translated by Al Poulin, Jr., clippings, typescripts, 1973 September-October; 6 (Box 98)
  - Florist's cards, undated (Box 98)
  - Nordhaus, Jean: The Porcelain Apes of Moses Mendelssohn, typescript, biographical info, 1995 December (Box 99)
  - Wachsteter, Gregory Alan: A Slight Crack in Sanity, typescript, undated (Box 99)
  - Dixon, K. Reynolds: Digital Projection, typescript, 1996 January (Box 99)
  - Dings, Fred: Roses, Coals, typescript, 1996 January (Box 99)
  - Mnookin, Wendy: Do You Love Me Now?, typescript, 1995 January (Box 99)
  - Keplinger, David: Arabesque, typescript, 1996 January (Box 99)
  - Scates, Maxine: Forgiveness, typescript, 1995 August (Box 99)
  - Dixon, K. Reynolds: Collection of Poems, typescript, 1995 September (Box 99)
  - Whitney, J.D.: Collection of Poems, 1995 September (Box 99)
  - Spence, Michael: Adam Chooses, typescript, 1995 September (Box 99)
  - Gibson, Becky Gould: Body of the Goddess, typescript, 1995 September (Box 99)
  - Young, Brian: He'll, typescript, 1995 September (Box 99)
  - Watson, J.C.: Collection of poems, typescript, undated (Box 99)
  - Waldner, Liz: Collection of poems, list of presentations and publications, 1995 November (Box 99)
  - Ashwander, D.S.: Selected Letters, published copy, 1990 (Box 99)
  - Murabito, Stephen: The Oswego Fugues, typescript, 1995 June; 3 (Box 99)
  - Berryhill, Michael: Athena's Garden and Other Poems 1968-1995, typescript, 1995 November (Box 99)
  - Chase, Karen: The ABC of What I've Been Called, typescript, [undated] (Box 99)
  - Neumeyer, Peter F: Collection of Poems, typescript, 1995 September (Box 99)
  - Morales, Harry: List of Poems of Mario Benedetti, biographical info, 1994 November (Box 99)
  - Cox, Mark: The Chair of Forgetfulness, typescript, list of poetry published, 1995 October (Box 99)
  - Maher, Adrienne: Lighter than Air, typescript, 1995 November (Box 99)
  - Jasper, Matt: Collection of Poems, typescript, undated (Box 99)
  - Crosby, William H.: The Poems of Catullus, typescript, undated; 3 (Box 99)
  - Heyen, William: Crazy Horse in Stillness, corrected galleys, 1995 September; 4 (Box 99)
  - Heyen, William: Crazy Horse in Stillness, page proofs, corrected, 1996 (Box 99)
  - Addonizio, Kim: Jimmy and Rita, typescript, undated (Box 99)
  - The Southern Review, 1994 (Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous: correspondence and authors' submissions, 1994-1996, undated; 4 (Box 99)
  - BOA Editions: History/Overview 1976-1983, [circa 1983] (Box 100)
  - BOA Editions: History/Overview 1977-1985, [circa 1985] (Box 100)
  - Irwin, Mark: Quick, Now, Always, galleys, 2nd Copy, 1996 (Box 100)
  - Museum Pieces. Poems on Painting and Sculpture, typescript, undated; 2 (Box 100)
  - Irwin, Mark: Correspondence; Quick, Now, Always, typescript, undated (Box 100)
  - Biespiel, David: On Earth as in Heaven, typescript, 1988 January; 3 (Box 100)
  - Le Six Juin 1944-Jour-J: Les Mots et les Choses, Bertrand Mathieu; Final Critical Responses to BOA's Recommendations: manuscript, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Foerster, Richard: miscellaneous materials; various materials; miscellaneous folder, [1992-1995] (Box 100)
  - Minnesota Calls: Magazine: Nov/Dec 1993 issue; Jan/Feb 1994 issue; Barton/Sutter reception itinerary, 1993-1994 (Box 100)
  - Miscellaneous: correspondence; clippings; booklet of poems by G. de la Vega; copy of Poet Lore; copy of Webster Review; authors' submissions; book reviews; managing editor's report., 4 (Box 100)
  - Crosby, William H.: Miscellaneous correspondence, [1994-1995]; 2 (Box 100)
  - CAP VI page proofs, 1995 August; 17 (Box 100)
  - CAP VI: permissions to reprint, 1995 August; 5 (Box 101)
  - CAP VI fees, 1995 August; 3 (Box 101)
  - Ignatow, David: Sunlight: A Sequence for My Daughter 1979, Hall, Donald: The Toy Bone, book cover, North Atlantic Review: A Literary Guide to the City of Light. Special Section: Poems Toward the Millennium, 1979-1995, undated (Box 101)
  - BOA Editions Necessary Voices: BOA Poets Read/ '94 [~20 copies], undated (Box 101)
  - BOA Editions: catalogue and prospectus, 1977-1980 (Box 101)
  - Assorted proofs, 2 (Box 101)
  - Collection of Poems: broadside, printed, undated (Box 101)
  - Logan, John: Collected Fiction, book cover, undated; 2 (Box 101)
  - Hébert, Anne: Selected Poems, book cover, undated (Box 101)
  - Laux, Dorianne: Awake, two bookcards, undated (Box 101)
  - Makuck, Peter: The Sunken Lightship, bookcard, undated (Box 101)
  - Piccione, Anthony: Anchor Dragging, bookcover, undated (Box 101)
  - Laux, Dorianne: What We Carry and other poems, galley proof, page samples, 1994 (Box 101)
  - West, Deb: fax cover letter to Stern, Gerald, undated (Box 101)
  - Snodgrass, W.D.: Remains, bookcover, undated (Box 101)
  - Lyon, Rick: Bell 8, Bookcover, undated (Box 101)
  - Byrne, Edward: Along the Dark Shore, bookcover, undated (Box 101)
  - Laux, Dorianne: What We Carry and other poems, galley proof, page samples, 1994; 3 (Box 101)
  - Cendrars, Blaise: Christmas at the Four Corners of the Earth, translation by Mathieu, Bertrand: galley proof, 1994; 8 (Box 102)
  - Bly, Robert: Gratitude to Old Teachers, typescript and two published booklets, 1993 (Box 102)
  - Lyon, Rick: Bell 8, typescript, 4 (Box 102)
  - Kostelanetz: Wordworks, miscellaneous papers, 1993-1994 (Box 102)
  - Kenvin, Natalie: Bruise Theory, bound manuscript copies, circa 1993; 3 (Box 102)
  - Doud, William E.: play manuscript, 1994 April (Box 102)
  - Huff, Steve, correspondence re Christmas at the Four Corners of the Earth by Blaise Cendrars; manuscript copy, 1993-1994; 3 (Box 102)
  - "Letters"; correspondence with BOA poets, 1992-1993 (Box 102)
  - Sutter: includes bound manuscript copy (uncorrected proofs) of The Book of Names by Barton Sutter, 1993 (Box 102)
  - Sutter: correspondence with BOA, 1993 (Box 102)
  - Frauhammer correspondence re Hébert, 1993 (Box 102)
  - Addonizio: author slips, correspondence, miscellaneous, circa 1993-1994 (Box 102)
  - Booksleeves for Contemporary American Poetry, Ed. by A. Poulin, Jr., 6th ed., undated (Box 102)
  - Cover art: author photo, William Heyen, undated (Box 102)
  - Brochures for Contemporary American Poetry 6th ed., 1996 (Box 102)
  - Parallels: Artists/ Poets by Midmarch Arts Press: collection of poetry, undated (Box 102)
  - Miscellaneous note and pamphlet, undated (Box 102)
  - Folder with materials that "Have been logged in Review Journal 2 DBase/12/1/94", 1994 December (Box 102)
  - Book, Consortium: book sales and distribution: Spring and Summer 1996 (Box 102)
  - Enriching Our Lives: Poetry Lessons for Adult Literacy Teachers and Tutors, 1995 (Box 103)
  - Addonizio, Kim: The Philosopher's Club, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 103)
  - Lyon, Rick: Bell 8, bound manuscript copy, undated (Box 103)
  - Heyen, William: Crazy Horse in Stillness, poem, manuscript, galleys, and hard copy for printer, 1996; 3 (Box 103)
  - Heyen, William: Crazy Horse in Stillness, uncorrected index, undated (Box 103)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: The Führer Bunker: The Complete Cycle: Poems. Page proofs, 1995 (Box 103)
  - Frauhammer/Huff correspondence/Heyen page proofs, miscellaneous, [circa 1995] (Box 103)
  - Consortium: Book Sales and Distribution, Inc.: info. packet, 1993-1995 (Box 103)
  - Calyx: A Journal of Art and Literature by Women; BOA Advertisements and ad info for Archive, undated (Box 103)
  - Cendrars, Blaise: page proofs, 2 bound copies, 1 unbound copy of Christmas at the Four Corners of the Earth, 1994 (Box 103)
  - Frauhammer/Huff correspondence, Snodgrass c.v., Francille Rusan Wilson c.v. and essay, "This Past was Waiting for Me When I Came" and other miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 103)
  - Consortium Book Sales and Distribution. New Titles: Fall and Winter/95/96, 1995-1996 (Box 103)
  - Consortium Book Sales and Distribution. New and Complete Titles Catalog: Spring and Summer 1994 (Box 103)
  - Knott, Bill: manuscript copy, The Quicken Tree: Poems, 1995 (Box 103)
  - Knott corrections: The Quicken Tree: Poems, manuscript copies, corrected proofs, 1995; 2 (Box 103)
  - Knott, Bill: manuscript copy, corrections for The Quicken Tree, poems, 1995 (Box 103)
  - Knott, Bill: The Quicken Tree, uncorrected proofs w/ scanned cover pages, [circa 1995] (Box 103)
  - Knott, Bill: The Quicken Tree, various materials regarding enclosed manuscript copy, circa 1995 (Box 104)
  - Heyen, William: Crazy Horse in Stillness, Poems, bound copy, uncorrected Proofs, 1996 (Box 104)
  - Blank BOA checks, brochures for BOA Editions, Ltd., Fall/Winter 1994, New Titles and Complete Backlist (6 copies), and Lannan Literary Videos Catalog, 1995, undated (Box 104)
  - Heyen Final/BOA Editions/Crazy Horse, 1996; 12 (Box 104)
  - Patrick, William B.: These Upraised Hands: Poems. Galleys/1st corrected copy, 1995; 2 (Box 104)
  - Patrick, William B.: Patrick's Corrections, 1995; 2 (Box 104)
  - Patrick, William B: These Upraised Hands: Poems. Galleys/ 2nd copy, 1995; 2 (Box 104)
  - Knott, Bill: The Quicken Tree, a Book of Poems. Uncorrected Proofs, undated; 3 (Box 104)
  - Letters/Correspondence re Knott, The Quicken Tree, 1995 (Box 104)
  - Knott: The Quicken Tree, production materials and other miscellaneous, undated (Box 104)
  - Lake Affect Magazine Winter 1994, miscellaneous scanned cover pages, miscellaneous correspondence, undated (Box 104)
  - Knott, Bill: The Quicken Tree, book mockup, 1995 January 8 (Box 104)
  - News from BOA Editions Ltd.: reviews, 1995 September-November (Box 104)
  - Piccione, Anthony: For The Kingdom, manuscript copy, 1992 October (Box 104)
  - Nye, Naomi Shihab: Red Suitcase, Poems, manuscript copy, 1994 (Box 104)